<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Apna Kissan</string>
    <string name="Alluvial_soil">
Alluvial soil is highly fertile and typically found in river valleys. It is composed of silt, sand, clay, and organic matter deposited by rivers. This soil type is rich in nutrients like potassium and phosphorus, making it ideal for agriculture. Crops that thrive in alluvial soil include rice, wheat, sugarcane, cotton, and vegetables. Its well-draining properties and fertility are beneficial for various other crops, too. This soil is prevalent in regions like the Indo-Gangetic Plain, making it a backbone for agricultural productivity in those areas</string>
    <string name="Clayey_soils">
Clayey soils are heavy and dense, retaining water effectively but draining poorly. Rich in minerals and nutrients, these soils are highly fertile but can be challenging to work with due to their stickiness and compact nature. Crops that thrive in clayey soils include rice, which requires waterlogged conditions, and root crops like potatoes and carrots. Additionally, legumes such as beans and peas benefit from the nutrient-rich environment. This soil type is often found in lowland areas, contributing to robust agricultural yields when managed properly</string>
    <string name="Laterite_soil">
Laterite soil, rich in iron and aluminum, forms in tropical, high-rainfall areas through intense weathering. Known for its reddish color and low fertility, it’s often acidic and poor in organic matter. However, with adequate fertilization and irrigation, laterite soil supports crops like tea, coffee, rubber, coconut, and cashew nuts. Its also suitable for certain fruits such as pineapple and banana. In addition, this soil is often used for pasturelands and growing vegetables, particularly those that tolerate acidic conditions. Proper soil management practices are crucial for maintaining productivity in laterite soils</string>
    <string name="Loamy_soil">
Loamy soil is considered ideal for farming due to its balanced mix of sand, silt, and clay. This combination provides good drainage, nutrient retention, and aeration. Loamy soil is rich in organic matter, making it highly fertile and capable of supporting a wide variety of crops. Farmers love loamy soil for growing vegetables like tomatoes, carrots, and onions, as well as grains such as wheat and corn. Fruit crops like strawberries and melons also thrive in this type of soil. Its versatility and fertility make loamy soil a top choice for diverse agricultural production</string>
    <string name="Sandy_loam">
Sandy loam is a well-balanced soil type that combines sand, silt, and a bit of clay. It offers excellent drainage while retaining enough moisture and nutrients for plant growth. This soil is easy to work with, making it a favorite among gardeners and farmers. Sandy loam supports a wide variety of crops, including root vegetables like carrots and potatoes, as well as beans, lettuce, and spinach. Additionally, fruit trees such as apple, peach, and citrus thrive in this type of soil. Its versatility and fertility make sandy loam ideal for diverse agricultural practices</string>
    <string name="Sandy_soil">
Sandy soil has large, gritty particles that ensure excellent drainage but offer low nutrient and water retention. This soil warms up quickly in spring, creating an extended growing season but requires frequent irrigation and fertilization. Despite its challenges, sandy soil is suitable for root crops like carrots and potatoes, as well as melons, cucumbers, and peanuts. Certain herbs, such as thyme and rosemary, also thrive in sandy conditions. Its quick-draining nature makes it ideal for crops needing less water, but consistent management is necessary to maintain soil fertility</string>
</resources>